Let's go back to coding the content provider. The first
of the required content provider methods we're going to implement
is getType. getType is used to return the mime type
associated with the data at the given URI. We use
the URI matcher we built earlier to match the given
URI against the expressions we've compiled in. For each match,
we return a unique mime time, that starts with either
V and D Android cursor item, for a single record or
V and D Android cursor dir for multiple items.
We've nicely already defined these strings in our WeatherContract, in
our tests, we're getting the type. We're going to compose
URIs, using the standard methods we have, inside of our
WeatherContract. Then, we're going to pass these in to
our content provider, through the ContentResolver. Which is how you
call all functions in content provider. And we're going to
make sure it matches what we have in the contract.
I've placed the actual values as comments so you can
see, really, what's going on. Note that some of these returning
type directory, which means they're going to return a list
of different items in their cursor. While others are returning type
item, which means they will only return a single item.
Next, we're going to have you finish up getType. You're going to add
the appropriate cases in this switch statement. But to return mime
types, the remaining URI types that we aren't yet handling. No,
there are only two to add, and they
really look just like the ones in WeatherContract.